

CONTACT

San Salvador, El Salvador.

AGE: 31 years old PHONE: (503) 2248 3570 CELLPHONE: (503) 7967 1371

EMAIL:

salvadorortiz.91@gmail.com

REFERENCE\$

Personal

Elida Ruiz Cel. 7900 0644 Juan Cerna Cel. 7989 6258 Kelly Sanabria Cel. 6316 1685

Professional

Ing. Adán Mauricio Navas

Project Manager (Colon's Town Hall) Tel. 2346-5767

MHR. Roberto Efraín Reales

Human Resources Manager (Colon's Town Hall) Tel. 2346-5768

MAF. Fátima Cecilia Ramírez

Finance Manager (Colon's Town Hall) Tel. 2314-2917

Lic. René Gerardo Meléndez

Development Coordinator (UCA) Tel. 2210-6600 ext. 932

Ing. Guillermo Enrique Fernández

Network Coordinator (UCA) Tel. 2210-6600 ext. 915



RODOLFO SALVADOR ORTIZ CASTILLO

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science
 "José Simeón Cañas" University (UCA)

ADDITIONAL

- Amazon Web Services (AWS)
 Udemy Academy (2022)
- Management Coaching Certified FEPADE (Dec, 2021)
- Management Leadership Certified FEPADE (Nov, 2021)
- Municipal Administrative Management Certified Higher School of Public Administration (Dec, 2020)
- Scrum Developer Certified
 Don Bosco University (Sep, 2018)
- Software architecture for multi-tenant application Certified ADYSA S.A. de C.V. (Jun, 2015)

ABOUT

I am a software engineer with **8 years of experience** software development. Experience with **Python, Django, Rest API, Unit Testing, SQL, Docker, full stack web development and refactoring.** I also have knowledge and experience (1+ year) with AWS (S3, Lambda, VPC, EC2), PHP and Symfony, but I definitely prefer work with Python.

Highly skilled in leadership, proactive, responsible and self-motivated. Along with these skills I worked as a Chief Technology Officer (CTO) in Colon's town hall.

I am looking forward to bringing these skills to a new position as a full-stack developer.

LANGUAGES

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Creativa Consultores
 Full Stack Developer
 (Jul 2022 Present)
- Colon's Town Hall Chief Innovation Officer (May 2021 – Jul 2022)
- "José Simeón Cañas" University (UCA)
 Project Lead and Full Stack Developer (Oct 2016 – May 2021)
 - Full Stack Developer (Oct 2015 – Oct 2016)
- FESA El Salvador
 Full Stack Developer (Freelance)
 (May 2016 Jan 2017)
- American Franchise Coorporation Community Manager (Nov 2011 – Feb 2013)